

Manali Pen

Email: manali.sunil.pen@gmail.com

Phone No: +91 8850320296

Passionate, Innovative and a proven team player, I am a Bachelor of Computer Engineering with 3.5+ years' experience on Quality Assurance, Automation and Manual testing. I hope to share my skills, expertise and experience with your team and valuable clients.

Technical Proficiency:

Automation Tools: Selenium with Java, Test Automation Center (TAC), Accenture

Duck Creek Applications Platform (ADAP), TestNG, Jenkins,

PuTTY, WinSCP, SoapUI

Frameworks: BDD, Page Object Model

Defect management tools: HP ALM, JIRA

Programing language: Java

Database and IDEs: Oracle, Eclipse, NetBeans

Operating System: Windows

Key Skills:

- Experience in Software Quality Assurance Testing, proficient in testing Desktop and Web based applications based on **Manual and Automation testing**.
- Strong knowledge of **SDLC** and **STLC** including Requirement analysis (queries and clarifications with BA), creating design documents, developing, and implementing Test plans, creating Test estimation and Test approach, writing Test cases and Test scenarios, and their execution, Defect logging and tracking.
- My insurance testing work profile involved handson experience in Duck Creek Policy Testing, XML based log testing, **SQL** server technology.
- Designed and implemented test cases which thoroughly addressed all requirements and specifications; results demonstrated a less than 1% defect leakage.
- Reported and tracked defects with comprehensive details that enabled developers to understand the defect quickly without having to collect additional data.
- Always willing to take up challenges and take advantage of the new learning areas.
- Strong oral and written communication skills.
- Participated and contributed to **Agile** team activities.

Professional Experience:

BNP Paribas Sr. Test Engineer Mar 2021 - Present

Project Name: CASE(Controls Automation Sanction and Embargoes)

- Involved in writing, reviewing, executing test cases and raising defects in defect tracking tool Jira.
- Responsible for converting manual test cases into Automation script(BDD framework) by identifying test cases for automation.
- Maintained already existing automation scripts during refinement.
- Performed deployment on continuous integration tool Jenkins.
- Responsible for CASE migration using PuTTY and WinSCP.
- Involved in running scripts in SoupUI to get responses for web services.

Accenture Software Engineer Jan 2018 - May 2020

Client: DCT Westfield

- Design Test Scripts and Tested applications based on requirements to meet client specific customization in the insurance domain
- Worked on complex and 100% client specific Underwriting testing to evaluate risk associated with a policy in terms of patterns, pricing and Authority Level calculation.
- Used ADAP tool for complex Underwriting testing which reduced manual efforts by 40%
- Prepared Software testing plans, estimating, and reviewing QA efforts as part of the overall development effort
- Prepared KT documents on several functionalities
- Performed Component Testing, Smoke Testing, Agency Portal and Duck Creek Integration testing and System testing.
- Created, maintained and ran automation smoke test scripts on Selenium tool using Java.
- Worked as a point of contact between onshore and offshore System Testing teams and solve queries or discrepancy between both the teams
- Responsible for test planning, Creation of test cases, Executing test cases and logging defects
- Defects are logged and tracked in HP ALM
- Helped new joiners in understanding the application and providing necessary KT sessions

Accenture Associate Software Engineer Nov 2016 - Dec 2017

Client: Vodafone UK

- Tested applications based on requirements to meet client specific customization in the communication domain
- Tested replica created of original database to view user data so that huge traffic is not created on original DB
- I have worked in Customer Centric Service team on Siebel user interface
- Responsible for test planning, Creation of test cases, Executing test cases and logging defects
- Defects were tracked and took till closure on HP ALM and JIRA tool
- Performed Component testing, Regression testing and Sanity testing
- Automated, maintained and ran Sanity test script using Selenium with Java.
- Automated and designed Page Object Model framework for prepaid and postpaid scripts and updated it according to requirement change using Selenium.
- Have worked with multiple releases and teams at same time by implementing Agile based methodology

Certifications:

- ISTQB foundation level Certified
- Insurance Foundation Training (IFT) Certified

Education Qualification:

University of Mumbai, India Bachelor of Computer Engineering June 2016

Referees:

Yatin Patil Aakansha Dalvi

Team Lead, BNP Paribas Team Lead, Accenture Tel: +91 9960149987 Tel: +91 9833882259